mtgprice.com 2017-12-10

# MTGPrice.com Privacy Policy

### 1\. Introduction

Thanks for choosing MTGPrice. To provide you with the MTGPrice Service (or “Service”, both as defined in the Terms and Conditions of Use), Quantitative Methods, Inc. dba MTGPrice (“MTGPrice”, “we”, “us”, “our”) needs to collect some information about you, and this Privacy Policy is where we describe the information we collect, what we do with it, and how you can manage and control the use of your information. By using or interacting with the Service, you are entering into a binding contract with us and consenting to the use of your information as explained in this Privacy Policy. If you don’t agree with these terms, then please don’t use the Service.

### 2\. The information we collect

**2.1** Registration data:  

When you sign up for the Service, we may collect information we ask you for, like your username, password, e-mail address, date of birth, gender, postal code, and country. We may also collect information you voluntarily add to your profile, such as your mobile phone number and mobile service provider. If you connect to the Service using your Google credentials, you authorize us to collect your authentication information, such as your username, encrypted access credentials, and other information that may be available on or through your Google account, including your name, profile picture, country, hometown, e-mail address, date of birth, gender, friends’ names and profile pictures and networks. We may store this information so that it can be used for the purposes explained in Section 3.   

**2.2** Usage & log data:

When you use the Service, we automatically collect certain information, including:

 **(i)** Information about your type of subscription and your interactions with the Service, including with advertising, products and services which are offered, linked to or made available on the Service;

**(ii)** The details of the queries you make;

**(iii)** Technical data, which may include the URL you are coming from, your IP address, unique device ID, network and computer performance, browser type, language and identifying information, transactional information enabling digital rights management, and operating system; and

**(iv)** Location information. If you have connected your account to Google, we may receive similar information related to your interactions with the Service on Google. We may store this information so that it can be used for the purposes explained in Section 3. 

**2.3** Other Services:  

You may integrate your MTGPrice account with third party services besides Google (“Other Integrated Services”). If you do, we may receive, use and share the categories of information described above, including information made publically available on or through your account of such Other Integrated Service, in accordance with this Privacy Policy.   

**2.4** Payment data:  

When you sign up for a Trial or any of our Paid Subscriptions (as defined in the Terms and Conditions of Use), or make other purchases through the Service, your credit card information and other financial data that we need to process your payment are collected and stored by third party payment processors, and we may collect some limited information, such as your postal code and details of your transaction history. These third parties generally provide us with some limited information related to you, such as a unique token that enables you to make additional purchases using the information they’ve stored, and your card’s type, expiration date, and last four digits.   

**2.5** Cookies & similar technologies:  

A cookie is a small text file that resides on your computer, mobile phone, or other device, and allows us or our business partners to recognize your device when you return to the Service. We may use cookies to perform functions essential to the operation of the Service, track site usage and trends, provide advertising on the Service, and improve and customize your MTGPrice experience. We may also allow certain business partners to place or recognize cookies for those purposes. Learn more about how we use cookies and other similar standard Internet technologies at the bottom of this Privacy Policy.

### 3\. How we use the information we collect:

We may use the information we collect, including your personal information, to:

 **(i)** Provide, personalize, and improve your experience with the Service and products and services made available through the Service, for example by providing customized or localized content and advertising;

**(ii)** Ensure technical functioning of the Service and products and services made available through the Service, develop new products and services, and analyze your use of the Service, including your interaction with applications, advertising, products and services that are made available, linked to or offered in the Service;

**(iii)** Communicate with you for Service-related purposes, including promotional e-mails or messages;

**(iv)** Enable and promote the Service, including features and content of the Service and products and services made available through the Service, such as sharing, user interactions, notifications and suggestions, and integration with third party services;

**(v)** Enforce this Privacy Policy, the Terms and Conditions of Use, and the Mobile Terms, including to protect the rights, property or safety of MTGprice, users or any other person and the copyright-protected content of the Service; and

**(vi)** as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy.

### 4\. How we share the information we collect:

We may share the information we collect, including your personal information, as follows:

 **4.1** Sharing with Google and other services:  

If you connect to MTGPrice using Google or otherwise connect your MTGPrice account to an Other Integrated Service, the default setting is generally that MTGPrice automatically shares your activity and activity-related stories with that service. You understand that such information may be attributed to your account on Google or the Other Integrated Service and may be published on such service. See section 5 below to learn how you can disable sharing of information on Google and Other Integrated Services. You understand and agree that Google’s or other third parties’ use of information they collect from you is governed by their privacy policies, and MTGprice’s use of such information is governed by this Privacy Policy.   

**4.2** Sharing with Third Party Applications:  

To personalize your experience, we may share some information we have collected about you with providers of Third Party Applications, such as high-level geographic information, your musical preferences, settings and technical data. However, we take precautions to prohibit Third Party Application providers from attempting to identify you by using the information we provide to them or by collecting additional information without your consent. Please note that if you: actively choose to provide Third Party Applications with additional information, such as by visiting a Third Party Application (which enables collection of your IP address) or allowing us to share precise geographic data which Third Party Application providers request from us; or consent to collection of additional information about you by a Third Party Application provider when you for example register with or log in to the Third Party Application, the Third Party Application may be able to identify you and associate the information previously provided by MTGPrice with you. You agree and understand that a Third Party Application provider’s privacy policy governs its use of your information that we provide to it or that it collects from you.   

**4.3** Service providers and others:  

We may from time to time engage other companies in the MTGPrice group and third party service providers to perform functions and process user data, consistent with section 3 above. Third party service providers’ processing of user data will always be subject to security and confidentiality obligations consistent with this Privacy Policy and applicable law.   

**4.4** Other sharing:  

In addition to the above, we may also share your information to third parties for these limited purposes: to allow a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets; to respond to legal process (e.g. a court order or subpoena), if we believe in good faith that it is necessary to do so; to comply with requirements of mandatory applicable law; to protect the safety of any person; to protect the rights and property of MTGprice, including to enforce the Terms and Conditions of Use and Mobile Terms; and to address fraud, security or technical issues; to inform business partners about use of the Service and products and services made available through the Service, in the form of aggregated statistics or otherwise in a format which does not reveal your identity; if you expressly opt in to such sharing. You agree and understand that the privacy policies of the third parties will govern all use of information that we provide to it or that it collects from you.

### 5\. Links

We may display advertisements from third parties and other content which links to third party websites. We cannot control or be held responsible for third parties’ privacy practices and content. Please read their privacy policies to find out how they collect and process your personal information.

### 6\. Security

We are committed to protecting our users’ information. Your password protects your user account, so you should use a unique and strong password, limit access to your computer and browser, and sign off after having used the MTGPrice Service. While we take reasonable data protection precautions, no security measures are completely secure, and we do not guarantee the security of user information at any time.

### 7\. Children

For users in the United States, the MTGPrice Service is not directed to children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, do not use the Service and do not provide any personal information to us. If we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we will delete it.

### 8\. Accessing and updating user information

You can access and amend some of the information we keep on you through your settings. To learn more about the information we store about you, e-mail privacy@MTGprice.com. We will respond within a reasonable period of time upon verification of your identity.

### 9\. Contact us

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at webmaster@MTGprice.com.

### 10\. Changes to the Privacy Policy

We may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please visit this Privacy Policy regularly. If we make changes which we believe are material, we will inform you through the Service. Your continued use of the Service thereafter constitutes acceptance of the changes.

### 11\. More information about cookies & similar technologies

**11.1** We use cookies for four general purposes, as explained below:

  * _Essential Operational:_ These cookies are necessary to allow us to operate the MTGPrice Service as you have requested. For example, they let us recognize what type of subscriber you are and then provide you with services accordingly.

  * _Performance:_ We use these cookies to analyze how the MTGPrice Service is used or is performing. We use this information to maintain, operate and continually improve the MTGPrice Service.

  * _Functionality:_ These cookies let us operate certain functions of the MTGPrice Service in line with the choices you make. These cookies mean that when you come back to the MTGPrice Service, we can provide you with our services as you have asked for them to be provided, such as knowing your username, remembering how you have customized our services and reminding you of music you have enjoyed.

  * _Targeting/Advertising:_ We use these cookies to serve you with advertisements through the MTGPrice Service. Some advertisements may be relevant to you and your interests. These cookies may also help us and our business partners regulate the advertisements you receive and measure their effectiveness.

**11.2** As above, our business partners may use their cookies on the MTGPrice Service, for the same general purposes identified above. For more information about the use of cookies and how to block them, visit www.allaboutcookies.org, www.youronlinechoices.eu (Europe) or www.aboutads.info/choices/ (United States).

**11.3** Most web browsers also allow you to manage your cookie preferences. You can also set your browser to refuse cookies, or delete certain cookies. This may impair or prevent due functioning of the Service in doing so, though.

**11.4** We may use standard Internet technologies similar to cookies like these:

  * _Clear GIFs:_ We may use “clear GIFs” (aka “web bugs”), which are small image files that we embed into our e-mail newsletters, to learn whether you opened or forwarded the newsletter or clicked on any of the content. This information tells us about our newsletters’ effectiveness and helps us ensure that we’re delivering information that you find interesting.
  *  _HTML5 Local Storage:_ We use HTML5 local storage for frequency capping purposes and to provide you with relevant advertising. We do not use HTML5 local storage to collect any personal data or to track your activity on our websites.
